### LEON FARDELL

50 Stanley St, Richmond, Victoria 3121 • 0466906134 • Leonfardell134@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

A motivated and confident 23-year-old looking to further their career in insurance with experience in the insurance industry and particularly investigations and intelligence. A keen eye for detail and a passion for delivering results on their files and striving to learn more and find further expertise in the field. A demonstrated ability to coach others and display their technical expertise in an understanding way.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Investigations Review Officer, Fraud & Intelligence

Jul 2022 – Present

Suncorp - Melbourne, VIC

- Investigating a portfolio of home insurance claims referred to the Fraud & Intelligence team.
- Meeting all KPI's and KPA's
- Excellent understanding of the investigations process.
- Trained in investigative interviewing and document interrogation.
- Excellent understanding of all IT systems used during the investigations process, and this can be adapted any environment.
- Understanding of relevant legislation including the insurance contracts act and the insurance code of practice.
- Understanding of importance intelligence and its practical applications to the investigation process.
- Regularly liaised with intelligence analysts and collaborated to ensure the investigation process is well equipped with the tools and information necessary to conduct a thorough and fair investigation.

#### **Claims Specialist**

Jul 2021 – Jul 2022

Suncorp - Melbourne, VIC

- Taking Inbound calls and actioning customers home insurance claims in a timely and positive manner
- Working knowledge of claims handling systems such as In4mo and claim centre.
- Discussing policy coverage and setting customers claim up for success.
- Ability to independently make claims decisions and provide authority on processes and internal business knowledge.
- Strong use of department feedback solutions and always looking for ways to better the processes that are followed.
- Took initiative to be a part of high support sessions for new starters and stepping up to run these sessions when coaches were sick / out of the office.
- Was an approachable source of knowledge for other specialists on my team.

#### **Window Covering Installer**

Sep 2020 - Jul 2021

Classic Blinds & Shutters. - Cardiff, NSW

- Manufacturing of plantations shutters & window coverings including being a part of the installation team
- Attended customers' homes and conducted work professionally and independently in a time productive manner
- Liaised with customers and gained experience in working closely with their expectations while simultaneously meeting business performance & quality standards
- Working in a factory adhering to manufacturing standards and keeping a clean workspace

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Business (Economics & Finance)**

**Present** 

Currently studying
RMIT - Melbourne, VIC

# ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Technically proficient with computers
- Fast typing speed
- Extensive knowledge of programming
- Knowledge of Microsoft office
- Strong knowledge of Insurance & Finance Industry
- Ability to coach others and convey knowledge in professional and approachable way